迈克:现在,卢克,我告诉你,这个叫"电锯决斗"的游戏可好玩了.
Mike: Now, Luke, I'm telling you, the graphics on "chainsaw duel" are amazing.
好,现在,你进攻,按这个键.
Okay, now, to attack you press that button.
卢克:哦,我砍断你的腿了!
Luke: Oh, I just crosscut your leg off!
卢克和迈克:哦!哇!
Luke and Mike: Ohh!Eww!
杰森:账单,账单,杂志的泳装版.还有你的明信片,
Jason: Bills, bills, swimsuit edition of "Psychology Today."
卢克.你爸爸寄来的.你不想看看吗?
And here's a postcard for you, Luke.From your dad.You're not gonna read it?
卢克:他的明信片每张都一样.
Luke: These postcards are all the same.
总是世上最大的什么东西的照片,汽车一样大的鳟鱼,
It's always a picture of the world's biggest something.
四层楼高的玉米热狗.
A trout the size of an RV, a four-storey corndog...
杰森:你给他回过信吗?
Jason: You ever write him back?
卢克:寄到哪去啊?
Luke: And send it where?
杰森:哦,这是我见过的最大的萝卜.
Jason: Well.That is the biggest radish I have ever seen.
我觉得你该看看,卢克.
I think you ought to take a look at this, Luke.
卢克和迈克:哦!哇!
Luke and Mike: Ohh!Eww!
卢克:抱歉,西沃医生,你说什么了?
Luke: Sorry, Dr.Seaver, did you say something?
杰森:看起来,你爸爸要来这里看你了.
Jason: Looks like your dad is coming here to see you.
杰森:乔治还没到吗?
Jason: Is George here yet?
迈克:爸爸,不知道他是不是要把卢克绑架,
Mike: Dad, how do we know that he's not gonna kidnap Luke,
把他带到哪个外国去,
and take him to some foreign country,
然后给他做整容手术,好让我们认不出他来.
and have plastic surgery done so we don't recognize him?
杰森:这个风险我们必须要冒.
Jason: That's just a chance we're gonna have to take.
行了,迈克,
Come on, Mike, has it ever occurred to you that Luke is looking forward
你就没想过卢克也盼着看看他的爸爸吗?
to seeing his dad?
卢克:他还没到?
Luke: Isn't he here yet?
杰森:看?
Jason: See?
卢克:我只是想快点结束.
Luke: I want to get this over with.
杰森:我想他随时都可能到.
Jason: I'm sure he's gonna be here any minute now.
可他有辆大卡车要照顾.
He's got that big truck to deal with.
迈克:是的,他很难把他的18轮的特大型卡车停到咱们家前面.
Mike: Yeah, he can't exactly park his 18-wheeler in front of our house.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
迈克:爸爸,爸爸.他想把那大家伙横着停在那里.
Mike: Dad, dad.He, he's gonna try to parallel park that big rig.
杰森:他会办到的.相信我.他会办到的.他办到了.
Jason: He's not gonna make it.Trust me.He's not gonna make it.He made it.
乔治:你们好,各位.我是乔治.
George: Hello, everybody.I'm George.
杰森:嗨,乔治.
Jason: Hi, George.
乔治:嗨,卢克.
George: Hey, Luke.
杰森:哦,呃,请进,请进.
Jason: Oh, uh, come in.Come in.
卢克:真不相信你把卡车开到这里来了.
Luke: I can't believe you drove your truck here.
乔治:呃,哦,卡尔顿大酒店的门童不让停在那里.
George: Uh, well, the valet at the Ritz Carlton wouldn't take it.(laughing)
(笑)呃,卢克,你为什么不把我介绍给他们呢.
Uh, Luke, why don't you introduce me to your foster family.
卢克:呃,这是西沃医生.
Luke: Uh, this is Dr.Seaver.
乔治:医生!
George: Doctor!
杰森:精神病医生.
Jason: Psychiatrist.
乔治:啊,别难为情.那你一定是 西沃太太了.
George: Ah.No shame in that.And you must be Mrs.Seaver.
麦琪:哦,乔治.很高兴见到你.
Maggie: Oh, George, it's very nice to meet you.
乔治:呃,请原谅,但你的皮肤是我见过最好的,比电影明星的都好.
George: Uh, excuse me, but you have the most gorgeous movie-star skin I have ever seen.
麦琪:哦,乔治,你真会开玩笑.不过,杰森,请记录下来.
Maggie: Oh, George, that's a load of hooie, but Jason, take notes.
杰森:这是我的女儿--克莉丝.
Jason: That is our daughter, Chrissy.
克莉丝:很高兴见到你.
Chrissy: Pleased to meet you.
乔治:你好.
George: Ma'am.
克莉丝:他的脖子一点不红.
Chrissy: His neck isn't red.
杰森:那是,呃,我们的儿子迈克,你们认识.
Jason: That's, uh, our son Mike.You know Mike.
迈克:嘿,呃,是的.很高兴见到你,乔治.真遗憾,你不能待长点时间.
Mike: Hey, uh, yeah, good to see you, George.It's a shame you can't stay long.
乔治:哦,实际上,
George: Well, actually, I do have a couple hours to kill before I deliver
在把那些西红柿送到皮斯卡塔韦之前我还有一两个小时的富裕时间.我想也许灭亡可以去吃点早饭.
these tomatoes to Piscataway.I thought maybe we could go grab some breakfast.
卢克:我吃过了.跟我的家人们.
Luke: I already ate.With my family.
乔治:我给你带了些东西.呃,
George: I brought you something, uh, a little memento of your mother.
是你妈妈留下的.愿她的灵魂安息.
God rest her soul.
迈克:哇,乔治,
Mike: Wow, George, you, uh,
你,呃,
came all this way just to deliver something to Luke you could'a dropped
一路风尘仆仆为卢克送东西来,为什么不寄过来呢?
in the mail?
乔治:哦,一些东西太重要了,
George: Well, some things are too important to stick in the mail,
放在邮包里不放心.比如这些我和卢克以及他妈妈在一起的照片.
like these snapshots of me and Luke and his mom.
杰森:迈克,能帮我,呃,把这图片在墙上抻一抻吗?
Jason: Mike, do you want to help me, uh, straighten the picture over here on this wall?
迈克:不.
Mike: No.
杰森:我没问你.
Jason: That wasn't a question.
乔治:呃,这是你一岁生日的时候,
George: Uh, it's of your first birthday, uh,
我和你妈妈带你去看世界上最大的辐条轮胎.
your mom and I took you to see the world's biggest radial tire.
卢克:谢谢.我待会再看.
Luke: Thanks, I'll look at them later.
本:爸爸,妈妈在为8000人做意大利面条吗?是你,乔治布鲁沃尔,
Ben: Dad, is mom making spaghetti for about 8,000 people?
很喜欢比基尼岛海滩的明信片.嘿,那些是最大的……
Yo, George Brower, loved that postcard
from Bikini Beach.Man, those were the biggest
杰森:本!
Jason: Ben!
乔治:你看起来不错,小朋友.
George: You're looking good, big buddy.
本:我希望姑娘们也这么想.今晚,我要参加最精彩的晚会.
Ben: I hope the babes think so.I've got the most incredible party tonight.
杰森:你愿意过来帮我和迈克抻一抻这些图片吗?
Jason: Do you want to come over here and help me and Mike straighten out the pictures?
本:不.
Ben: No.
迈克:没问你.
Mike: It wasn't a question.
乔治:卢克,呃,我来这里不仅仅是送照片.
George: Luke, uh, I'm not here just because of the snapshots.
过了泽西后,我要穿越蓝岭山脉,
After Jersey, I'm cutting through the Blue Ridge Mountains where the
那里的萤火虫跳舞就像成千上万的流星.
fireflies dance like a thousand shooting stars.
你愿不愿意跟你的老爸爸做个伴呢?
What do you say, you keep your old man company?
卢克:听着,我已经告诉过你了,我不想跟你一起生活.
Luke: Look, I thought I told you, I don't want to go live with you.
乔治:我不是要把你从这些好人身边带走.我只是想你也许愿意花一两周的时间更好地了解你的爸爸.
George: I'm not trying to take you away from these fine people.I just thought
you might like a couple of weeks to get to know your dad better
卢克:什么,然后再像陌生人那样分开吗?
Luke: What, and work our way up to being strangers?
乔治:我不勉强你.(叹气)哦,
George: I won't push it.(sighing) Well, I appreciate your hospitality.
我很感激你们的盛情款待.呃,我该去运西红柿了.
It's, uh, time for me to haul my tomatoes out of here.
我要,呃,留给你们一箱"自然力量"生产的最好的西红柿.然后我就上路了.
I'll just, uh, leave you a crate of Mother Nature's finest juicy reds, and I'll be on my way.
迈克:哦,谢谢你,乔治.不过,我们不能接受.
Mike: Uh, thanks anyway, George, but we couldn't possibly accept.
杰森:哦,迈克,白送的西红柿.
Jason: Oh, Mike, free tomatoes.
迈克:好吧,谢谢,乔治.
Mike: Okay, thanks, George.
乔治:呃,箱子在……在门廊里.
George: Uh, well, the crates on....it's on the porch.
迈克:(叹气)哦,这次见面短暂而甜蜜.
Mike: (sighing) Well, that was short and sweet.
乔治:(尖叫)
George: (screaming)
乔治:(尖叫)别紧张,
George: (screaming) Take it easy, guys.
伙计们.人的后背上有47条肌肉.
There's 47 muscles in the back,
我的每一条肌肉都在跳动.
and every single one of mine is doing the watusi.
迈克:这,呃,有点意思.你不觉得吗,
Mike: It's uh, its kind of interesting, don't you think, George,
乔治,你刚要走,你后背就开始发病了?
that your back went out just as you were getting ready to leave?
嘿,小心!一只蜘蛛.
Hey!Look out!A tarantula!
乔治:是活板门蜘蛛还是漏斗网蜘蛛?哦,不是,只是一只毛球蜘蛛.
George: Trap-door or funnel-web species?Uh, nope, just an old hairball.
卢克:你干什么?
Luke: What are you doing?
乔治:我,呃,只是在试探一下.
George: I was, uh, just testing.
本:好了,我们能吃一顿三道菜的饭了.
Ben: All right, we got a perfect three-course meal.
冰镇啤酒,猪肉皮以及咸腌奶酪.
Icy Mug root beer, pork rinds, and Uncle Salty cheese logs.
迈克:我打赌一定很好吃,是不是,
Mike: I betcha that looks good, doesn't it, George.
乔治?我打赌你都等不及想尝一尝了,是不是?
I bet you can't wait to just dig in, huh?
乔治:等不及了!哦,如果你能的话,呃,往这边移一下.
George: Can't wait!Uh, if you could, uh, just scoot that right over here.
乔治:谢谢你.现在,我基本上能看到饭菜了.
George: Thank you.Now I can almost see that food.
杰森:乔治,这是我的朋友--克莱默医生.
Jason: George, here's a friend of mine, Dr.Kramer.
克莱默:你好,乔治.
Kramer: Hello, George.
迈克:赌10块钱,他没什么事.
Mike: Ten bucks says it's nothing serious.
乔治:(喊叫)
George: (yelling)
克莱默:看来你的后背有点畸形.
Kramer: Looks like your back is in bad shape.
乔治:总比你疙疙瘩瘩膝盖漂亮多了..
George: A darn sight prettier than those knobby knees of yours.
克莱默:今天下午到我的办公室来.我给你拍张片子.
Kramer: Get in my office this afternoon.I need to take some X-rays.
乔治:啊,这只是背痉挛.
George: Aw, it's just a back spasm.It'll clear itself right...(groaning)...
自己就会好起来的……(呻吟)……甜软糖加威士忌土豆.
sweet jelly bean on a rotgut potato.
克莱默:这会让他减缓疼痛.
Kramer: This will take the edge off his pain
杰森:这会让他吃不成威士忌土豆.
Jason: This'll take the rotgut out of his potato.
乔治:我没时间拍X射线.我有一卡车西红柿,
George: I don't have time for X-rays.
必须在今晚运到泽西去.
I've got a truckload of tomatoes that's got to be in Jersey by tonight.
迈克:哦,我们很想帮助你,
Mike: Well, I wish we could help out, George,
乔治,但我们不知道谁会驾驶那么大的卡车.
but we don't know anyone who could drive a truck that size.
本:你肯定能对付那大家伙吗?
Ben: Are you sure you can handle this thing?
杰森:嘿,比开救护车运那些吵吵闹闹的孩子们容易多了.
Jason: Hey, it's a lot easier than driving that clinic bus full of screaming
哈!西红柿不会在十字路口停车时向你哈气.
children.Ha!Tomatoes don't try to pants you at the intersection.
本:我们能开的快点吗?爸爸,
Ben: Can't we go any faster?
要是我不能按时赶回晚会该怎么办啊?
Dad, what if I'm not back in time for the party.
杰森:哦,别担心.一趟才用3个小时.
Jason: Oh, come on, it's a three-hour trip each way, Ben.
本,你有足够的时间.我现在开的速度也不慢.
You're gonna make it in plenty of time.I'm going at a decent speed.
本:那么,如果有只怀孕的母牛从我们右边过来的怎么办?
Ben: Then how come there's a pregnant cow passing us on the right?
杰森:行了,本,别紧张.我带你出来的原因是我认为我们两个可以好好地兜兜风.
Jason: Come on, Ben, relax.The reason I drafted you for this, is I thought it would be a nice outing for you and me.
本:哦,我们的帽子搭配的不错.
Ben: Oh, the matching hats were a nice touch.
杰森:很好.我们为什么,呃,
Jason: All right.Why don't we, uh, make up some names,
编几个名字呢?这样我们可以进行民用波段谈话,好吗?
and we'll talk CB talk, all right?
本:待会也许可以.我不想这么快就过于兴奋.
Ben: Maybe later; I don't want to peak too soon.
杰森:你想起个什么头衔呢?
Jason: What do you want your handle to be?
本:长头发之子.
Ben: Son of big hair.
卢克:你午饭没怎么吃.
Luke: You haven't touched your lunch.
乔治:哦,你迈克哥哥把菜推的老远,我够不着.谢谢.卢克?
George: Well, your buddy Mike keeps putting it just out of reach.Thank you.Luke?
卢克:什么?
Luke: What?
乔治:高中上的怎么样?
George: How's high school?
卢克:你为什么想了解?
Luke: Why do you want to know?
乔治:我从没进一个高中看一眼.
George: I never saw one from the inside.
卢克:是啊.哦,我们很多人有艰苦的休息时间.
Luke: Yeah.Well, a lot of us have had tough breaks.
乔治:打球吗?
George: Playing balls?
卢克:我还有事要做.
Luke: I think I've thing to do.
乔治:啊,求你了,卢克,求……哦,
George: Aw, come on, Luke, come...
告诉我,上帝,我该怎么接近自己的儿子.
Please, God, tell me how to get through to my son.
迈克:你,呃,你跟别人讲话吗,乔治?
Mike: You, uh, you talking to somebody, George?
乔治:哦!(笑)不,不,只是,呃,用嘴巴思考.
George: Oh!(laughing) No, no.Just, uh, thinking with my mouth.
有人说下巴上的肌肉是整个身体上最强壮的,但,
You know they say the jaw muscles is the strongest in the whole body,
呃,在路上独自颠簸了25年后,它变成了最没用的肌肉了.
but, uh, after 25 years on the road, I say it's the gluteus maximus.
就像拉丁语说的"废物".
That's Latin for "big butt."
迈克:是的,是的,我懂.我教法语.哦,嘿,来吧,乔治.我们得去,呃,得去拍片子.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, I know.I teach French.Well, hey, come on, George.We gotta get going and, uh, get those X-rays.
乔治:哎呀!哎呀!不用.我感觉好多了.
George: Ow!Ow!No need.I'm feeling much better.
迈克:是的,对,对.
Mike: Yeah, right, right.
你知道,乔治,
You know, George, you really should have said that you had something that
你真的早应该说你身上有什么毛病拍片很难看出来,比方说长疮,
wouldn't show up on an X-ray, like, uh, whiplash, or, uh,
得鸡眼,有口腔溃疡什么的.
hoof and mouth disease.
乔治:第一次见面的坏印象让你念念不忘,是吗?
George: That bad first impression burned you deep, didn't it?
迈克:对此念念不忘的是卢克.
Mike: Not half as deeply as it burned Luke.
乔治:那么我明白了,迈克.
George: So I see.Mike, I spent 25 thousand miles thinking about it.
我走了25000英里的路在考虑这个问题.卢克是我的亲骨肉,
The thing is, Luke is my blood.
我自己就是想去了解父亲的时候已经太晚了.
I never got to know my dad until it was too late.
我不想让卢克也这样.
I don't want that to happen to Luke.
麦琪:是的,谢谢你来电话.
Maggie: Yes, thank you for calling.
迈克:我真不敢相信这个乔治.
Mike: I can't believe this George.
装着受伤而让让卢克感动.
Pretending he's hurt to get on Luke's good side.
麦琪:他不是假装的,迈克.
Maggie: He's not pretending, Mike.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪:刚才是克莱默医生.他跟乔治的医生谈过了.
Maggie: That was Dr.Kramer.He's spoken to George's doctor.
乔治的背已经恶化了.如果他不停止开车的话,
George's back has deteriorated to the point,
他就会瘫痪的.
where if he doesn't stop driving his truck, he's going to be paralyzed.
乔治:医生们称之为脊椎老损.
George: The doctors call it cervical deterioration.
我认为就是脖子老疼.
I call it a pain in the neck.
迈克:那,你不开车会干什么呢?
Mike: Well, what are you gonna do when you stop driving?
迈克:乔治,医生说如果你不停止,你会瘫痪的.
Mike: George, the doctors say if you don't, you're going to be paralyzed.
乔治:啊,
George: Aw, they don't know nothin'.
他们什么都不懂.他们告诉我的朋友比利·鲍伯还有3个半月时间好活,
They told my friend Billy Bob he had 3-1/2 months to live.
可他活了4个半月.
He lived 4-1/2 months.
迈克:乔治,换工作就这么难吗?
Mike: George, what's so hard about changing jobs?
乔治:凭8年级的教育程度,我能干什么?
George: With an eighth grade education?
也许我可以当个大法官.
Maybe I could be a supreme court justice.
我只知道三件事:卡车,卡车和卡车.
I only know three things; that's trucks, trucks, and trucks.
迈克:哦,我相信你可以得到其他的工作.
Mike: Well, I'm sure there's other jobs you could get, that, uh, you know,
呃,你知道,你还可以围绕卡车找工作啊.
you could still be around trucks.
乔治:比方说?
George: Like what?
迈克:哦,我不知道.
Mike: Well, I don't know.You could, uh, you could lease big rigs.
你可以,呃,你可以出租卡车;你可以经营个卡车车站;
Or you could run a truck stop.
你还可以买可以张贴的漂亮女人的剪影图.
Or, uh, you could sell those little silhouettes of girls they stick on
mudflaps.
乔治:那不是卖的;那是世代相传的.
George: Those aren't sold; they're handed down from generation to generation.
迈克:那么,你什么时候告诉卢克这事?
Mike: So, when are you gonna tell Luke?
乔治:卢克不该知道这事.我不要他的可怜.我只是想要个更好了解他的机会.
George: Luke is to know nothing about this.I don't want his pity.I just want a chance to get to know him better.
本:三个小时的行程.他们是在骗傻子呢.
Ben: A three hour trip.That's what they told Gilligan.
杰森:好了,看来我们有点迷路了.
Jason: Okay, so we got a little lost.
本:有点迷路!爸爸,
Ben: A little lost!Dad, we were halfway to Florida!
我们都快到佛罗里达了!如果不是在那家加油站停下来的话,我们现在都到古巴了.
If we hadn't stopped at that gas station, we'd be in Cuba by now.
杰森:好了,现在我们走上正确的道路了.
Jason: Well, we're going the right way, now.
那个仓库就在路前面半英里的地方.
The depot's a half a mile down the road.
本:爸爸,都7点半了.
Ben: Dad, it's 7:30!
如果他们2分钟卸完车,
If they unload the truck in two minutes,
而且如果我们以没小时195英里的速度回到家,
and if we drive 195 miles per hour back home,
我才可以赶上那个晚会的最后5分钟.
I might actually be able to catch the last five minutes of that party.
杰森:能这样就好了.
Jason: Could be worse.
本:正确.你还可以唱一唱威利·纳尔逊的歌呢.
Ben: True.You could still be singing those Willy Nelson songs.
杰森:好了,仓库到了.
Jason: Ah, here's the depot right up here.
我们跟他们说一下,让他们以最快的速度把车上的西红柿卸下来,
We're going to get them to unload our tomatoes just as quickly as they can.
杰森:嘿,打扰一下.我们有一车西红柿,该怎么处理,
Jason: Hey, excuse me.We have, uh, tomatoes, what do we do with them?
仓库工人:拉到19号码头,伙计.
Depot worker: Pull 'er into dock 19, Johnny.
杰森:(唱歌)好的,太好了.我说,他们能马上卸车呢?
Jason: (sighing) All right, great.Listen, these guys are gonna unload us right away?
仓库工人:你一定是新来的.司机卸自己车上的货.
Depot worker: You must be new to this route.Drivers unload their own trucks.
卢克:(唱歌)你不拽超人的斗篷,你不向风里吐口水,你不拉……
Luke: (singing) You don't tug on Superman's cape, you don't spit into the wind, you don't pull....
迈克和卢克:(唱歌)……拉下孤独老流浪汉的面具,你不在吉姆身上浪费时间.
Mike and Luke:  (singing)...pull the mask off the old Lone Ranger, and you don't mess around with Jim.
迈克:我喜欢这首歌.
Mike: I love that song.
卢克:是的,小时候,妈妈经常给我唱这首歌.
Luke: Yeah, mom used to sing it to me when I was a baby.
迈克:是吗?
Mike: Yeah?
卢克:看看这张照片.我是不是很像她?
Luke: Check out this picture.Don't I look a lot like her?
迈克:哦,是的.哦,嘿,乔治看起来真年轻.你笑起来跟他一样,你知道吗?
Mike: Oh, yeah, gosh.Hey, George looks so young here.You got his smile, you know it?
卢克:不,我没看出来.
Luke: Nah, I don't see it.
迈克:嘿,卢克,呃,我想跟你说件事.哦,我真的不想,可……
Mike: Hey, Luke, uh, I want to talk to you about something.Well, I really don't, uh...
卢克:迈克,如果你想跟我谈生活的真谛,
Luke: Mike, if you're trying to talk about the facts of life,
那你有点晚了.
you're a little late.
迈克:如果你爸爸继续开车的话,他会瘫痪.
Mike: If your dad keeps driving a truck, he's going to be paralyzed.
卢克:什么?
Luke: What?
迈克:是的.他不听医生的.
Mike: Yeah.He won't listen to the doctors, and he sure won't listen to me.
当然他也不听我的.我觉得你应该知道这事.
And I thought you'd want to know.
本:(笑)我觉得最后有一半的西红柿是在我们身上了.
Ben: (laughing)I think we ended up with half the tomatoes on us.
杰森:(笑)
Jason: (laughing)
本:哦.你看.掉进西红柿箱柜的时候,你该看看自己的脸.
Ben: Oh, yeah?You should have seen your face when you fell into the tomato bin.
杰森:哦,刚才我还在散步呢,转眼就在红海里畅游了.我很幸运,乔治拉的不是化肥.
Jason: Well, I was walking along, and the next minute I'm swimming in the red sea.I'm just glad George wasn't hauling fertilizer.
本:哦,那个工头还对几个工人说,我们的活干的不赖呢.
Ben: Well, the foreman said for a couple of city boys, we did all right.
杰森:本,看来你是没办法赶去参加今天的晚会了.
Jason: Ben, there's no way you're going to make your party tonight, and,
呃,这全是我的错.我真的很抱歉.
uh, it's all my fault, and I am truly sorry.
本:我很开心,爸爸.收到了吗,伙计?
Ben: I had a great time, dad.Copy, good buddy?
杰森:10-4.(笑)哦,我们收拾停当,向家开拔.
Jason: 10-4.(laughing) Well, let's hammer down, and head for home!
本:(拉绳索)好啊!
Ben: (pulling horn cord) Yee-hah!
乔治:(呻吟)我不是故意吵醒你的.
George: (groaning) I didn't mean to wake you up.
卢克:你在干什么?
Luke: What are you doing?
乔治:我只是在挪我这把老骨头到厕所去方便.
George: Just trying to get this old body to the bathroom and pay the toll.
卢克:哦,你一定很疼吧.
Luke: Oh, you must really be in pain.
乔治:不,没什么.哇!让我这把愚蠢的老骨头去死吧.
George: Nah, it's nothing.Whoa!Slap me silly and shave me naked!
卢克:来,让我罢帮你.
Luke: Here.Let me help you up.
乔治:好的,我来了.我马上就到了.(笑)
George: Ok, I'm coming.I'll be right there.(laughing)
卢克:怎么这么乐啊?
Luke: What's so funny?
乔治:哦,
George: Well, when you were a little boy,
你小的时候,我经常半夜带你上厕所,
I used to take you to the bathroom in the middle of the night so that
这样你就不会尿床了.
you wouldn't wet the bed,
你看现在,我们好像换了人似的.
and now it seems like you're doing the same thing for me.
卢克:是的,哦,我一点都不记得了.
Luke: Yeah, well, I don't remember anything back then.
乔治:我记得.要让你重新睡着只能给你唱最喜欢的那首歌.
George: I do.The only way you'd go back to sleep is if you heard your favorite song.
(唱)你不拽超人的斗篷,你不向风里吐口水……
(singing) You don't tug on Superman's cape, you don't spit into the wind....
卢克:是的!妈妈经常给我唱这首歌.
Luke: Yeah!Mom used to sing that to me.
乔治:卢克!你妈妈是个可爱的女人,
George: Luke!Your mom was a lovely woman,
可她唱歌老跑调.你还记得吗?
but she couldn't carry a tune in a bucket.Don't you remember?
你最害怕柜子里的那些妖怪了.(唱)你不拉下孤独老流浪汉的面具,
You were terrified of all those monsters in the closet.(singing) You don't
你不在吉姆身上浪费时间……
pull the mask off the old Lone Ranger, and you don't mess around with....
卢克:卢克.那就是你.
Luke: Luke.It was you.
乔治:你特别喜欢听.这样你就觉得自己比那些怪物更大,
George: You loved it.
更壮了.
Made you think you were bigger and stronger than any of those monsters.
卢克:真是你唱的?
Luke: You really did that?
乔治:是的,当然.(呻吟)
George: Yeah.Sure.(groaning)
卢克:听我说,迈克告诉我你后背的事了.
Luke: Look, Mike told me what's going on with your back.
乔治:啊,那个小子的舌头可真长啊.
George: Aw, that boy's tongue is loose at both ends.
卢克:你知道,乔治,你必须现在就做决定.
Luke: You know, George, you're going to have to make a decision here.
乔治:我决定了.我不会放弃开车的.我不想再谈这事了.
George: I made one.I'm not gonna quit trucking.I don't wanna talk about.Luke: So you're just gonna pretend like it doesn't exist?You know, that's typical.
卢克:你就这样假装什么事也没发生吗?你总是这样.
Luke: So you're just gonna pretend like it doesn't exist?You know, that's typical.
这就像在过去13年里,所有的事从来都没发生过一样.
Its just like everything that's ever went on in the past thirteen years
我想跟你谈谈,乔治.
never happened.I want to talk about it, George.
我是说,过了这么长的时间,你突然过来,对我说过去的事就让它过去算了.让我们跳上车,看萤火虫去吧.
I mean, you come here after all this time, and you say what's past is past.Let's jump into a truck and watch the fireflies.
乔治:我只是想……
George: What Is was trying....
卢克:听着!你给我一张接一张地寄世界上最大笨鸡的明信片.
Luke: Look!You send me postcard after postcard, about the world's biggest prairie chicken.
为什么不寄一张写着"对不起,我毁了你的生活"这样的明信片呢?
Well, what about the postcard that says "I'm sorry I ruined your life?"
乔治:卢克……
George: Luke...
卢克:你知道,你逃避医生就像逃避所有的事,
Luke: You know, you run from doctors the way you run from everything.
包括你自己的儿子.我有什么不对的?
Including your own son.What was wrong with me?
乔治:你有什么不对的?
George: What was wrong with you?
卢克:是.怎么了这是,乔治?你为什么不告诉我呢?
Luke: Yeah.What was it, George?Why can't you just tell me?
乔治:你这个样子,我不能跟你说.
George: I can't talk to you when you're like this.
卢克:你总是那个老样子.我觉得你变不了.
Luke: Then you haven't changed.I don't think you ever will.
乔治:卢克!卢克!
George: Luke!Luke!I'm not very good at this kind of talk.
我不知道该怎么说这样的话.如果非要说出来,那我就整个晚上努努力.
But if it's what it takes, I'll keep trying all night.
不过,你先得帮我到厕所里去.
But first, you've got to get me to the bathroom!
杰森:啊哈,你该早点看看我们,麦琪.我们开着车,风吹在脸上,前方是宽敞的道路……
Jason: Ah, you should have seen us, Maggie.There we were, the wind in our faces, the open road before us...
杰森和本:……内裤里满是西红柿.
Jason and Ben: ...and tomatoes in our shorts.
麦琪:哦,嗨,乔治.
Maggie: Oh, hi George.
乔治:早上好.这是你们俩吗?谢谢你们帮我把西红柿运到泽西.
George: G'morning.Is that you two?Thanks for running those tomatoes to Jersey for me.
杰森:啊,小意思,乔治.
Jason: Ah, piece of cake, George.
乔治:哦,你这么说太好了.有时候,他们故意为难第一次去那里的人,让他们"自己的货自己卸".
George: Oh, glad to hear it.Sometimes they try to pull a fast one on first timers, make 'em unload their own truck.
迈克:你今天看起来好多了,乔治.
Mike: You're sure looking a lot better today, George.
乔治:哦,是的.呃,我该出门上路了.
George: Uh, yep, uh, about time to hit the road.
迈克:你,呃,你要走吗?那好极了……我是说你身体好多了.
Mike: You, uh, you're leaving?Now that's great....that you're feeling better.
乔治:我的背弯的可以看到车轱辘了.
George: My back's loose enough for me to see over the wheel.
我可以一路顺利地到达图森城了.
I should make it to Tucson just fine.
迈克:那么你肯定开大卡车是你最好的选择吗?
Mike: So you're sure that driving that big rig is the best thing for you?
乔治:哦,绝对是.
George: Oh, absolutely.As soon as I get there, I'm gonna sell it,
我一到那里,就会把车卖了,然后从一个老朋友那里买个小店铺.
and by myself a truck stop from an old buddy.
迈克:你不再开卡车了?
Mike: You're quitting trucking?
乔治:是的,卢克是个很好的年轻说客.
George: Well, Luke's a very persuasive young man.
迈克:哇,卢克.你怎么做到的?你说了什么?
Mike: Wow, Luke.Well, how'd you do it?What'd you say?
卢克:我说我要跟他走.
Luke: I said that I'm going with him.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
卢克:只是一两个月而已,迈克.帮他安顿一下.
Luke: It's only for a couple of months, Mike.To help him set up.
迈克:你脑子里塞棉花了吗?别惹我生气.
Mike: Are you out of your cotton-picking mind?No offense.
杰森:迈克,注意.
Jason: Mike, a word.
迈克:爸爸,对不起.不过,我不会让他这么做的.
Mike: Dad, I'm sorry, but I can't let him do this.
杰森:哦,你只能认了.卢克必须去了解自己的父亲.
Jason: Well, you have to.Luke has to get to know his father.
迈克:爸爸,他,他不能就这样拍屁股走人啊.他的生活怎么办?我们呢?
Mike: Dad, he, he can't just pick up and leave like this.What about his life?What about us?
杰森:迈克,这不是你的决定.
Jason: Mike, this is not your decision.
卢克:迈克,你教过我,有人最需要你的时候,
Luke: Mike, you taught me what it means to be there when somebody needs
你必须在他那里.我也想这么对乔治,我指的是我的爸爸.
you the most.And I want to do the same for George.I mean, my dad.
卢克:好了,伙计们,
Luke: Come on, you guys, don't look like that.
别哭丧着脸.只是一两个月而已嘛.我会回来的.
It's only for a couple of months.I'll be coming back.
迈克:(叹气)好吧,你一定要回来.
Mike: (sighing) Well, uh, you'd better come back.
卢克:别拦着我了.
Luke: Try and stop me.
麦琪:再见,卢克.
Maggie: Bye, Luke.
杰森:再见,卢克.
克莉丝:再见,卢克.
00:22:38,000
Jason: See you, Luke. Chrissy: Goodbye, Luke.